Did you sleep well?
Yeah.
I haven't slept this well in a long time.
Really?
Yeah.
You're so cute.
But you're cuter.
Claire, stop teasing.
What are you doing?
Can I get a hug?
Sure, but I smell like food.
Let me smell.
You don't smell bad at all.
I do.
Smells amazing to me.
It stinks.
Can't you see I'm cooking?
I smell like sausages all over.
Can I have a taste?
Hold on a sec.
Yes, Chief Ed.
Yes, you'll definitely have it by tomorrow.
Got it.
My editor called for the draft again.
But I still have no idea about an ending.
You can do this, fighting!
Cher also messaged me to hurry up.
Once I'm done, I'll come straight to you.
I'm sorry, Claire.
But this novel has to be absolutely perfect.
The tears streaming down his cheeks...
Are the sweetest taste of failure.
Such a profound description, Ms. Writer.
This is crazy, so crazy!
I can't take this.
It's just too much.
What are you rambling about?
I just feel so bad for her.
Feel bad for who?
For Warin, of course.
Is that your ex? Doesn't sound familiar.
Hey, are you crazy? This Warin.
This! This Warin right here!
The male lead in this novel.
Look.
Why? Did the male lead die?
Did she find someone new?
Ugh, no! Listen to me.
The male lead didn't want love.
Because of his past family trauma.
But he finally opened up to her.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Then what happened?
Look.
"The tears streaming down his cheeks...
...are the sweetest taste of failure."
How did Eris even come up with this?
We're her fans for a reason.
But now that I think about it...
The plot sounds a lot like your story.
I wonder...
Maybe my life is just a generic plot.
So people just easily use it for drama.
Hello there.
Ms. Eris!
Perfect timing!
I'm reading your new novel right now.
How did you come up with this line?
"The tears streaming down his cheeks...
...are the sweetest taste of failure."
Cher.
Ms. Eris...
is a famous novelist.
She knows exactly what to write to get people hooked.
Claire, please listen to me first.
Are you here to celebrate your views?
Or are you just here for more data?
When you wrote about
"the sweetest taste of failure"
Did you mean how I feel being used?
Or the money piling up in your account
because you sold my secrets for cash?
Well...
I gotta take Charcoal out for a walk.
I must excuse myself.
You know what
What makes me the angriest
is not that you wrote about me,
"The tears streaming down his cheeks...
...are the sweetest taste of failure."
Such a profound description, Ms. Writer.
Plus, the plot matches our story perfectly.
Claire, please don't misunderstand.
It's just a plot in a novel.
Other writers also draw inspiration from their surroundings.
Inspiration?
How dare you?
I thought I finally found my safe zone.
But clearly, I didn't.
Claire, please listen.
No.
To you, I'm just a fictional character you use for your writing.
But I'm sorry to say
This novel has come to an end.
Go back and write your perfect ending...
in your own fantasy world.
You made everything we had...
Feel like it was just your job.
It wasn't all like that, Claire.
I started this because of work, yes.
But then things got out of my control.
My feelings for you are completely real.
Real?
You're a writer.
You can't even tell truth from fiction, can you?
Even when we looked at each other...
You just saw me as words on a page.
Claire, Eris is sorry.
I admit it was really wrong of me...
to profit off of your life.
But I'm not here for research.
I'm here to ask for another chance.
Please, Claire.
Save it for someone else.
Cher, I'm sorry.
The person you should apologize to is Claire, not me.
This whole mess is my fault.
You should leave for today.
Let Claire cool down a bit, then you two can talk.
Alright.
What will you do about Ms. Eris?
Do nothing.
Hey, be serious.
I really don't think she meant it.
From what I know about her...
She seems like a good person.
Honestly, you know her better than I do.
Do you really think she did this on purpose?
Think about it carefully.
Claire.
I have nothing to say to you.
Wait a second, Claire.
This is the cancellation contract for the novel.
I'll delete the entire manuscript.
Even if it bankrupts me in fines, I don't care.
But Claire, I want you to know.
You're not just a generic plot.
You're the person I truly want a happy ending with.
So what?
This is the only copy in the world written just for you.
I've deleted all the files.
And these are my genuine feeling.
Chapter One: Claire is not a character.
But the one who taught me that
my heart to race whenever she's near.
Chapter Two: The scent of dogs on Claire
smells better than any expensive perfume
I've ever encountered.
Nonsense.
And the final chapter, Special Chapter.
This writer promises to take care of you for the rest of her life.
Let this story belong only to Claire and to us.
I made this to apologize for everything I did.
I know what I did was wrong.
I'm so sorry.
One
Two
Three
Four
Five
Six
Seven
I don't know why, but when I'm upset...
The only place I feel safe being weak...
Is right here with you, Claire.
I think I starting to like you.
I like you too.
My feelings for you are completely real.
Please forgive me.
Claire.
You weirdo.
In the end, love isn't like a novel.
It's about letting down your guard and being real with each other.
We might fall sometimes,
but as long as we learn
and write the next chapter together,
that's all that matters.
Excuse me, is this Love Lab?
Yes, it is.
The shop is so pretty. Just like the owner.
Thank you.
How can I help you today?
Do you have a girlfriend service?
Well, you'll have to try the service first to see if you like it.
If you do, we can talk.
Would you like to try it right now?